Justin Mao

<u>jmao.co</u> <u>github.com/justinmao</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/justinmao</u> justin@jmao.co 2307-5 St Joseph Street Toronto ON M4Y0B6 Canada (647) 949-1565

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Summer internship experience in software development at Nissan Motors
Freelance development/design work building an online platform for a hybrid/online fitness startup
Strong design skills developed as Creative & Media Director of Jane Goodall's Institute's Roots & Shoots:
University of Toronto Chapter
Volunteer work through Habitat for Humanity International in Sri Lanka and Indonesia

Bilingual in English and Mandarin Chinese **US citizen**

SKILLS

JavaScript (ES6), React.js, Express, Node.js, jQuery HTML/CSS, Sass
Python, SciPy/NumPy, pandas, TensorFlow
Java, Spring
SQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nissan Motors

Software Engineering Intern

Jun 2017 – Aug 2017 (3 Months) Guangzhou, China

JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, CSS

Java, Spring, MySQL, Oracle

- Built from scratch a high-profile component used by the Passenger Vehicle (PV) department to display WeChat/SMS promotional campaign information as well as statistics regarding their usage
- Automated data validation and resumption of corrupted or interrupted client data processes
- Created a tool for automatic generation of Excel spreadsheet summary reports
- Contributed to and debugged various data processing systems and visualization components

Freelance Web Developer/Designer

Nov 2017 – Present (Ongoing)

Toronto, Canada

.. _____

NOSUCHTHING training (nosuchthing.training)

JavaScript, React.js, HTML, Sass

Express, Node.js, WordPress (Headless)

- Designed and developed a web platform for the client to build an online presence/brand identity
- Integrated with existing SaaS components used by the client
- Provided server setup, administration, and maintenance
- Periodically worked with the client to iteratively collaborate on and improve features and UI/UX

EDUCATION

Honours Bachelor of Science (HBSc), Specialist in Computer Science University of Toronto

Sep 2014 – Jun 2018